{
    "id": "06ec3ff3b8e84223887ac425aada05a3",
    "title": "Present Continuous Or Present Perfect Continuous Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It …………… continuously since the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is raining",
                "has been raining",
                "was raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59c1e738832f48c59aa6b54a1f3ebb6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… him only once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am meeting",
                "have met",
                "have been meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8dc37413c0d4e628f45d84cd612afe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. him for a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not see",
                "have not seen",
                "does not see"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d289d43f36d46db92c18ba714460aaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children are hungry. They ……………… in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "played",
                "are playing",
                "have been playing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fefc2b27fe7b4d0b8029290294a3f853"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………… each other since our school days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knew",
                "have known",
                "have been knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07904b2a042140bfac42b191503b278c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you ………………… the job?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Have, completed",
                "Are, completed",
                "Have, been completing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfdcd1bb32274d798050275dbe462a3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her health …………….. considerably since she returned from the hills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has improved",
                "is improving",
                "has been improved"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1773c0a9049a492ebd256433008a5d80"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. to find our way home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have managed",
                "managed",
                "have been managing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f87b3b7676124e1d90bd4cb1820dbc91"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those who ……………. their work are free to go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "have finished",
                "have been finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db28da3ff80242848d399718d39a5a20"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the fifth time you ………………… that question.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "asked",
                "have asked",
                "are asking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7ef5a518a224561a5f7afbfd7725924"
        }
    ]
}